A Guide to the Grand Teton Lodge Company Records FA423
Rockefeller Archive Center
Grand Teton Lodge Company records
1926-1991
1946-1975
Rockefeller Archive Center
Grand Teton Lodge Company
FA423
14 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Grand Teton Lodge Company records were donated to the Rockefeller Archive Center in August 2003, by GTLC president Clay James.
File Plan
Former Classification: IV 3B 27
Related Materials
Related materials will be found in other Rockefeller Archive Center collections, including the Harold P. Fabian papers; the Kenneth Chorley papers; and the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Cultural Interests series.
Scope and Contents
The Grand Teton Lodge Company records consist of board materials, correspondence files, and financial records that document the company's operations in Grand Teton National Park from the 1930s to the 1980s. The bulk of the materials, dating from the late 1940s to the 1960s, concerns the development and renovation of tourist and lodging facilities in the park, and particularly the design, construction, furnishing, and remodeling of the new Jackson Lake Lodge, the cabins and facilities at Colter Bay, and the Jenny Lake Lodge.
Topics covered include the development of the park and the lodges. Early materials concerning the organization of the Grand Teton Lodge Company, concessions operations, and negotiations with the National Park Service and state representatives, are found in Harold Fabian's correspondence files from the 1930s-1940s, labeled Moran Operations and Jackson Hole. National Park Service files touch on the extension of Grand Teton National Park and the monument controversy, but also include studies of park development, concessions financing, and a 1965 survey of concession facilities in neighboring Yellowstone National Park. Other materials relating to interactions with the National Park Service, 1948-1950, are found in files for the GTLC's parent organization, Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc. The records also include JHPI board meeting materials for 1953-1969.
Files relating to the Lodge Company operations include accounting, construction, and general management and operations files; correspondence with architects and contractors; correspondence with Rockefeller or JHPI associates in New York, especially Allston Boyer and Kenneth Chorley; files concerning publicity and opening arrangements; and materials relating to transportation and other concession agreements. There is also a nearly full run of financial statements and/or audit reports for the period 1934-1985.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into four series: 1. Board of Directors; 2. Grand Teton Lodge Company; 3. Corporate Financial Records; 4. Photographs.
Biographical / Historical
The Grand Teton Lodge and Transportation Company was formed in 1936, following on a reorganization of the Teton Investment Company. Until their 1936 merger, the Teton Investment Company had been comprised of the Teton Lodge Company and the Teton Transportation Company, known collectively as the Teton Companies. The Transportation Company operated a bus service between Jackson Hole, the Union Pacific Railroad in Victor, Idaho, and Yellowstone Park, whereas the Lodge Company operated the Teton Lodge at Moran and subsequently the old Jackson Lake Lodge.
The Teton Companies were formed in the early 1930s, under the oversight of Harold Fabian, to provide transportation and lodging for visitors to the Grand Tetons. Harold Fabian's involvement in the region had begun a few years earlier with his appointment as vice president of the Snake River Land Company, an organization established in 1927 to provide for John D. Rockefeller Jr.'s land purchases in the Jackson Hole valley. The Snake River Land Company's purchases came with buildings as well as the land, and having acquired the two main lodges in the valley, it found itself in turn the main provider of services for visitors.
John D. Rockefeller Jr. had traveled to the Grand Teton area in 1924 and 1926 under the guidance of Yellowstone National Park Superintendent Harold Albright, and the visit inspired him to preserve the beauty of the region from unregulated development. The 1929 borders of Grand Teton National Park included the mountain range and the lakes abutting it, but they did not safeguard the surrounding valley. Under the guise of the Snake River Land Company, JDR Jr. bought up over 30,000 acres of private land within the Jackson Hole valley, for the express purpose of donating it to the federal government for an expanded Grand Teton National Park.
JDR Jr.'s efforts to donate his land met with prolonged local opposition. In 1943, President Roosevelt circumvented opposition by proclaiming much of the Jackson Hole valley a national monument. It was not until 1949 that Laurance S. Rockefeller was able to complete the formal transfer of land to the National Park Service. In 1950, a new, enlarged Grand Teton National Park emerged, combining the 1929 park and the monument lands.
With the rise in automobile travel and tourism in the postwar period, the park saw an increasing number of visitors, along with changes in the patterns of tourism. While protecting the valley from overdevelopment, there was also a need to provide additional and improved facilities for park visitors. Working through Jackson Hole Preserve Inc. (JHPI), the nonprofit conservation and education organization they founded in 1940, John D. Rockefeller Jr. and his son Laurance provided much of the funding needed to expand and improve tourist facilities in the park. JHPI purchased the Grand Teton Lodge Company, which then became a subsidiary of the nonprofit organization. The Lodge Company's leases with the National Park Service also made it the primary concessioner within the park.
In 1952 the Rockefellers and JHPI began planning and construction for a new Jackson Lake Lodge, which opened in 1955 as the first modern lodge within a national park. A second development at Colter Bay, funded jointly by the National Park Service and the Grand Teton Lodge Company, opened in 1957 and provided a range of accommodations, from rustic cabins (which had been preserved and moved from several locations within the park) to tent and trailer camping, as well as a cafeteria, general store, laundry, service station, marina, and museum. Colter Bay was an important pilot project in the National Park Service's Mission 66 program.
Grand Teton Lodge Company also developed a third lodge at Jenny Lake, on the site of the old Danny Ranch. Jenny Lake Lodge was a smaller and higher-end development of rustic cabins.
In 1955 the Grand Teton Lodge Company dropped the "and Transportation" function from its title, reflecting its heightened role in providing facilities for visitors who tended to prolong their stay in the valley and park.
- Board of Directors, 1945-1985; 1; 3.2 Cubic Feet 7 boxes
  Arrangement
  The Board of Directors series is arranged into four sets of files: Agenda, Correspondence, Minutes, and Executive Committee. Each file heading is arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  The Board of Directors series documents the general administration of the Grand Teton Lodge Company from the mid-1940s to the mid-1980s.
  The series is sorted by file type, but there is a considerable amount of overlap in the contents of the various Board files. The Agenda files for the most part include the full set of materials prepared for the board meetings. The Correspondence files concern meeting scheduling and arrangements and include a mixture of board materials.
  - Agenda
    Agendas include meeting topics and materials
    - 1947, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1953, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 2 pictures of construction at Jackson Lake Lodge, 1960 October 29; 2003:104:001 (Box 29)
      - 4 pictures of remodeling at Jackson Lake Lodge, 1960 October 29; 2003:104:002 (Box 29)
    - 1962 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Construction Drawing of Jackson Lake Lodge benches, 1966 August 25; 2003:104:029 (Folder 9)
    - 1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - 1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - 1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 1983 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - 1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence
    - 1945-1948 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - 1951-1953 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - 1955-1956 (1) (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - 1957 (1) (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - 1957 (2) (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - 1958 (1) (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - 1958 (2) (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - 1959 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - 1960 (1) (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - 1960 (2) (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - 1961 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - 1962 (1) (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - 1962 (2) (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - 1962 (3) (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - 1962 (4) (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - 1963 (1) (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Alternate Studies for Swimming Pools at Jackson Lake Lodge (Construction Drawing), 1963 July 9; 2003:104:003 (Folder 10)
    - 1963 (2) (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - 1964 (1) (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - 1964 (2) (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - 1965 (1) (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - 1965 (2) (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - 1966 (1) (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - 1966 (2) (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - 1967 (1) (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - 1967 (2) (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - 1968 (1) (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - 1968 (2) (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - 1969 (1) (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - 1969 (2) (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Minutes
    - 1949,1952-1956 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - 1960-1967,1969 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - 1971-1974 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Executive Committee
    - 1951,1956,1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - 1961 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - 1964-1967 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Grand Teton Lodge Company, 1926-1991; 2; 7.5 Cubic Feet 15 boxes
  The Grand Teton Lodge Company series is arranged alphabetically.
  The main topics of this series include the development of concessions and tourist facilities, operations, business and accounting, and correspondence.
  While files relating to a specific person or place may have their own heading, related documents may also be found under more general titles.
  - General, 1936-1938 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - General, 1940-1945 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - General, 1953, 1955-1956, 1958-1963 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Albright, Horace M. (Testimonial), 1949 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Attorneys (Patterson, Belknap & Webb), 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Accounts Receivable (1), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Accounts Receivable (2), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Barton, Robert S.: Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    Correspondence concerns park expenditures.
    Biographical / Historical
    Barton became treasurer of the Grand Teton Lodge Company in 1967. (The folder pre-dates this appointment).
  - Budget and Accounting, 1946-1949 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Budget and Accounting, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Budget and Accounting, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Cabins, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    The file contains photocopies of photos of cabins at Colter Bay, Moran, Jackson Lake Lodge, and Square G Ranch.
  - Colter Bay Project, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Colter Bay Project, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    "Specifications for Colter Bay Cabins," by Spencer, Lee and Busse, architects.
    File Plan
    1400
  - Concessions
    - General, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - General, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 85)
      LC 12-8
    - Horses, 1946-1956 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Horses, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Horses, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Feasibility Study Tack House Construction Drawing, 1963 April 15; 2003:104:004 (Folder 10)
    - Income, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Moran Store, 1946-1956 (Box 8, Folder 90)
      1002
    - NPS Business Permits, 1947-1955 (Box 9, Folder 91)
      1006-A
    - Harold Wiley (Boating), 1947, 1951-1955 (Box 9, Folder 92)
      1006-C
  - Construction: General, 1953, 1957-1965 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Construction:General, 1957-1970 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Construction: Request for Funds, 1955-1969 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Corporate (General), 1952 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Corporate Charter, 1926, 1929, 1936, 1946-1947, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    LC 1-A
  - Development Program, circa 1961 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Dude Rancher's Convention, 1947-1949 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    LC 11-1
  - Employee Retirement Plan: Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted- confidential material
  - Employee Retirement Plan: Correspondence, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Employee Retirement Plan: Documents, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Expense Accounts, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Furnishings: Budget Estimates, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - General Management, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    LC-5
  - General Management, 1948-1950 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Generators, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Green, John D.: Correspondence, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Harris, Kerr, Forster and Company (Auditors), 1955-1960 (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - History, 1930, 1945, 1953, 1955, 1958, undated (Box 10, Folder 110)
    Includes original letter signed by John D. Rockefeller Jr. conveying Snake River Land Company land holdings to the Grand Teton Lodge Company, 1945; and GTLC chronology.
    - Jackson Hole Brochure, circa 1940s; 2003:104:028 (Folder 9)
  - Income (Other), 1955 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Insurance, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    LC 8
  - Insurance, 1947-1950 (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Jackson Hole (Fabian Correspondence)
    Grouped by name of correspondent or subject.
    - 1933, 1940-1945 (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - 1943-1946 (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Jackson Hole Preserve Incorporated
    - Board Materials, 1953, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Board Materials, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Board Materials (1), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Board Materials (2), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Board Materials, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 120)
    - Board Materials, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 121)
    - Board Materials, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 122)
    - Board Materials, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 123)
    - Board Materials, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 124)
    - Board Materials, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 125)
    - General, 1959, 1965-1967, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 126)
    - Annual Report of Treasurer, 1956-1957 (Box 11, Folder 127)
    - Check Book, 1941-1945 (Box 11, Folder 128)
    - Donations, 1945-1948 (Box 11, Folder 129)
    - Ledger, 1945-1947 (Box 11, Folder 130)
    - National Park Service (1), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 131)
      JHP- 18, 307
    - National Park Service (2), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 132)
      JHP-18, 308
    - National Park Service, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 133)
      JHP-18, 309
      - National Park Service Organization and Functions Chart, 1950 October 10; 2003:104:005 (Folder 9)
        Retrieval times for maps and flat files may exceed 24 hours. Individual items may be restricted from access at the discretion of RAC.
    - Report on a Self-Insurance Plan, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 134)
    - Request for Funds, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 135)
    - Request for Funds, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Jackson Hole Wildlife Park, 1948-1951 (Box 12, Folder 137)
    Director's Report, WP 14
    - Map of Jackson Hole Wildlife Park, circa 1949; 2003:104:023 (Folder 9)
  - Jackson Lake Lodge
    - General, 1952-1955 (Box 12, Folder 138)
      1300
      - Assignment/ Floor Plans of Jackson Lake Lodge (Ground, 1st, 2nd floors), 1954 December 31; 2003:104:022 (Folder 9)
    - Business Concession Permit, 1947-1949 (Box 12, Folder 139)
      203-A
      - Jackson Lake Lodge Development (Grand Teton National Park, Jackson Hole National Monument), 1947 March 25; 2003:104:033 (Folder 10)
        Study, U.S. Department of the Interior, National Park Service. Drawing by Mattson, 1947 March 25. Inscribed on back: "August 20, 1947. This map given to Jack Alder at the Elbo by Mr. Mattson, this date." File 203-A, "Proposed - not actual."
    - Estimated Income and Expenses, 1953-1954 (Box 12, Folder 140)
    - Estimated Insurance Costs, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 141)
    - Estimated on Moving Buildings, 1952-1954 (Box 12, Folder 142)
    - Estimated Operating Personnel, 1950-1953 (Box 12, Folder 143)
    - Estimates: Jackson Lake Lodge Development, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 144)
      - Jackson Lake Lodge Development Construction drawing/ Site Plan, 1953 December 18; 2003:104:009 (Folder 10)
    - Functional Committee, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 145)
      1304 JLL
    - Furnishings (1), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 146)
      - Floor plans for Jackson Lake Lodge bedrooms (4 items), 1954 February- March; 2003:104:006 (Folder 9)
    - Furnishings (2), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 147)
    - Furnishings (3), 1954 (Box 13, Folder 148)
      - 6 photo negatives of Jackson Lake Lodge, circa 1954; 2003:104:007 (Box 29)
    - Furnishings, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 149)
    - Furnishings: Revised Budget, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 150)
    - Landscaping Work, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 151)
      - Planting at Jackson Lake Lodge (3 items) and Paving at Jackson Lake Lodge (1 item) (drawings), 1958 July 3; 2003:104:008 (Folder 9)
    - Morrison-Knudsen Company: General, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 152)
      1303 JLL
      Contracting company
    - Morrison-Knudsen Company: General, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 153)
    - Morrison-Knudsen Company: Insurance, 1952-1955 (Box 13, Folder 154)
      1303-D
    - Opening, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 155)
    - Project Authority, 1953 (Box 13a, Folder 156)
      1303-B
    - Remodeling, 1955, 1959-1960 (Box 13a, Folder 157)
    - Specifications and Agreement for New Main Stairway, 1956 (Box 13a, Folder 158)
    - Specifications Jackson Lake Lodge Development, 1953 (Box 13a, Folder 159)
    - Tax Assesment File, 1954-1955 (Box 13a, Folder 160)
    - Tax Assesment File, 1956 (Box 13a, Folder 161)
    - Underwood, Gilbert S.: Contract, 1952-1953 (Box 13a, Folder 162)
      1302-D
    - Underwood, Gilbert S.: Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 13a, Folder 163)
      1302-B
    - Underwood, Gilbert S.: Correspondence, 1953 (1) (Box 13a, Folder 164)
      1302-C
    - Underwood, Gilbert S.: Correspondence, 1953 (2) (Box 13a, Folder 165)
    - Underwood, Gilbert S.: Correspondence, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 166)
    - Underwood, Gilbert S.: Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - Jamieson, Francis A., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 168)
  - Jenny Lake Lodge
    - Opening, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 169)
    - Plans, 1951-1957 (Box 14, Folder 170)
      Contains only separated material
      - Preliminary Development Plan for Jenny Lake Ranch (construction), 1951 August 22; 2003:104:010 (Folder 10)
      - Powerhouse/Wiring Diagram, 1953 June 20; 2003:104:013 (Folder 10)
      - Existing Plot Plan-Development of Jenny Lake Lodge (blueprint), 1956 October 12; 2003:104:012 (Folder 10)
      - Temporary Alterations to Square G. Buildings at Jenny Lake Lodge (construction drawing), 1957 May 9; 2003:104:011 (Folder 10)
    - Rehabilitation, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 171)
    - Rehabilitation (1), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 172)
    - Rehabilitation (2), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 173)
    - Studio Purchase, 1958-1960 (Box 14, Folder 174)
      Crandall's Studio
      Related Materials
      Other material in Concessions:General, 1952-1953
  - Lillie, Raymond C.: Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 14, Folder 175)
  - Liquor License, 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 176)
    Stockade Room-Liquor License, Jackson Lake Lodge
  - Liquor License, 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 177)
    808-A
  - Meals on Wheels, 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Moran Operation, 1935-1936 (Box 15, Folder 179)
    510
  - Moran Operation, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 180)
  - Moran Operation, 1936-1942 (Box 15, Folder 181)
  - Moran Operation, 1937-1943 (Box 15, Folder 182)
  - National Park Service
    - General, 1925, circa 1930s, 1943 (Box 15, Folder 183)
      N-1007
      - Preliminary Park Development Outline Grand Teton National Park and Jackson Hole National Monument, 1943 November 10; 2003:104:014 (Folder 9)
      - Grand Teton National Park topographic map, circa 1930's; 2003:104:031 (Folder 9)
      - Map of Jackson Hole Area, 2003:104:030 (Folder 9)
      - Map of Teton National Forest, Wyoming, 1925; 2003:104:034 (Folder 10)
        Hand-colored map showing property held by Snake River Land Company, the Elk Refuge, and the federal government. Inscribed on back, "Map excluding Mormon Row"; and on front, "Received with Webb letter, March 13, 1930."
    - General, 1945-1947 (Box 15, Folder 184)
    - General, 1945-1948 (Box 15, Folder 185)
    - General, 1953-1955 (Box 15, Folder 186)
      N-1007 File plan numbers 203 (for Jackson Lake Lodge) and 901-B (for transportation services). Lodge permit originally filed as Real Estate - National Park Permit.
    - General, 1956-1959, 1961-1963, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 187)
      - Grand Teton Locator Map, 1976; 2003:104:032 (Folder 9)
    - Business Concession Permits, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 188)
      File plan numbers 203 (for Jackson Lake Lodge) and 901-B (for transportation services). Lodge permit originally filed as Real Estate - National Park Permit.
    - Concessioner Annual Reports, 1947-1953, 1956, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 189)
    - Concessions Contracts, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 190)
    - Concessions Contracts, 1952-1955 (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - Concessions Financing, 1959-1960 (Box 16, Folder 192)
    - GTNP Extension Bill, 1937-1938 (Box 16, Folder 193)
      Correspondence originally filed in National Park Service: Leases file.
    - Leases, 1930, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 194)
    - Leases, 1946-1953 (Box 16, Folder 195)
    - Park Development Conference, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 196)
    - Yellowstone Park Company Survey, 1952, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 197)
    - Yellowstone Park Company Survey, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 198)
    - Yellowstone Park Company Survey (1), 1965 (Box 16, Folder 199)
    - Yellowstone Park Company Survey (2), 1965 (Box 16, Folder 200)
    - Yellowstone Park Company Survey, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 201)
  - New York Office
    - Boyer, Allston
      - 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 202)
      - 1955 (Box 17, Folder 203)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 204)
      - 1959-1960, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 205)
    - Chorley, Kenneth
      President of the Grand Teton Lodge Company (1952-1963)
      - 1954 (1) (Box 17, Folder 206)
      - 1954 (2) (Box 17, Folder 207)
      - 1954 (3) (Box 17, Folder 208)
      - 1956 (Box 17, Folder 209)
        - Photo of rifle, 1956 April 20; 2003:104:016 (Box 29)
      - 1957 (1) (Box 17, Folder 210)
      - 1957 (2) (Box 17, Folder 211)
      - 1957 (3) (Box 17, Folder 212)
      - 1958 (1) (Box 17, Folder 213)
      - 1958 (2) (Box 17, Folder 214)